Wim von Benecke

Witrivier, Mpumalanga, South Africa



boneswvb@gmail.com



+27 (0) 71 099 2811



linkedin.com/in/wim-von-benecke-680429135

Summary

Experienced Office Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the business supplies and equipment industry and the hospitality industry. Skilled in Negotiation, Sales, Management. Strong information technology professional with a Full stack developer focused in Web app development from Zero To Mastery Academy. Advanced React training at Scrimba completed.

Experience



Office Manager/Web developer(PERN stack, JS, Node)

Madbookings

Aug 2020 - Present (1 year 8 months +)

In charge of all functionality of the whole company. Doing all the maintenance webwork for all the different websites of the company.

Admin / Human resources Manager at Madbookings

Madbookings

Dec 2018 - Aug 2020 (1 year 9 months)

Admin Manager

Madbookings

May 2018 - Aug 2020 (2 years 4 months)

Job Seeker

Job Seeker

Nov 2017 - Apr 2018 (6 months)

Administrator

Radio Vision

Mar 2017 - Oct 2017 (8 months)

Managed Account for Fridge Factory Warehouse and walk in customer. Admin all aspects

Administrator

Lowveld Service Centre

Feb 2014 - Feb 2016 (2 years 1 month)

Managing Of the following accounts - Electrolux, Whirlpool, The Fridge Factory, Master Care, Maxi Care, Teljoy, other smaller accounts and cash customers

Account Manager

Early Appliance Services

Mar 2013 - Jan 2014 (11 months)

Accounts Managed - Whirlpool, Electrolux, Some other smaller accounts

Retail Branch Manager

CC Chickens

Jan 2011 - Feb 2013 (2 years 2 months)

Retail Chicken Products

Retail Branch Manager

Fastrack

Feb 2009 - Dec 2010 (1 year 11 months)

Electrical house hold goods and disco equipment

Financial Clerk - temp

Vleismeester

Dec 2008 - Dec 2008 (1 month)

Temp position

General Manager

Chain Group Of Companies

Jan 2006 - Nov 2008 (2 years 11 months)

Plumbing, Electrical, Maintenance and Construction

Sales Representative

Profesional Field Marketinh

Jan 2005 - Dec 2005 (1 year)

Marketing of FMCG's

Sales Representative

collective Marketing

Jan 2004 - Dec 2004 (1 year)

Marketing of FMCG's

Co-Owner

prestige Home Center Nelspruti

Feb 2003 - Dec 2003 (11 months)

NQF 4 Trainer for cabinet making and wood machining. Registered with the FIETA Seta.

Assessor, Assessment developer and Moderator

Risk Consultant Manager

First National Bank

Mar 1991 - Jan 2002 (10 years 11 months) Admin/Human resources and financial

Corporal

South African Defence Force Jan 1988 - Jan 1991 (3 years 1 month) Military Police

Education



Advanced React

2020 - 2020

Advance React training by Scrimba - Presented by Bob Zirol

⊗z™ Zero To Mastery Academy

Full stack developer, Web app specialis 2019 - 2019 React, express.js and PostgressQl

(A) freeCodeCamp

Various certificats - Java Scrip front end developer 2018 - 2018

Nelspruit Hoërskool

Comercial 1983 - 1987

Licenses & Certifications

S Html Fundamentals course - Sololearn 1014-5786912

S CSS Fundamentals course - Sololearn 1023-5786912

SPHP Tutorial course - Sololearn 1059-5786912

JavaScript Tutorial course - Sololearn 1024-5786912

- Java Tutorial course Synergistx 1068-5786912 SQL Fundamentals course - Synergistx 1060-5786912 Moderate Assessment - ETDP SETA 47268 Plan and conduct assessment of learning outcomes - ETDP SETA 47268 Design and development assessment - ETDP SETA 47268 Module 1 - Spiritual growth, Church growth, Practical preaching, Old testament 1 - Nehemia Bible Institute Module 2 - Practical prayer, Leadership, Church organisation, Old testament 2 -Nehimia Bible Insitute Module 3 - Church stewardship, Youth work, Teacher training, Old testament 3 -Nehemia Bible Insitute Module 4 - Spiritual discernment, Kingdom of God, Evangelism, Old testament 4 - Nehemia Bible Insitute Module 5 - Marriage counselling, Family counseling, Community development, New testament 1 - Nehemia Bible Institute Module 6 - Woman's ministries, Church music, Liturgy, New testament 2 -Nehemia Bible Institue
- **Basic course in Theology With distinction** University of Pretoria/Universiteit van Pretoria

 P001132-01-2008

Diploma in Church Leadership - With Distinction - Nehemia Bible Institute

- Gevordere verkeerbeheer module South African Defence Force 701 pro 09
- Diploma in Mobile App Development (Destinction) Upskillist
- Advanced react programming Scrimba

Skills

Microsoft Office • Customer Service • Pastel Accounting • Account Management • Sales Management • Social Media • Sales • HTML5 • bootstrap • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Honors & Awards

Pulse Award - First National Bank
Apr 2001
Sales and service award

Pulse Award - First National Bank
Jul 2001

Sales and service award

Adrenalin Rush Award - First National Bank
Jul 2001

Sales and service award